Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Muriel Rukeyser Special with Jan Heller Levi, Suzanne Gardinier, and Adrienne Rich, 2006-11-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_70)
- Jim Hoberman on Borat; Vincent Panama Alba on Shooting of Sean Bell by NYPD, 2006-12-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_71)
- Alisa Solomon Interview with Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_59)
- Esther Kaplan and Abe Velez on FCC; Jed Abrahamian on Iran; Alisa Solomon Interviews Jody Rosen on Jewface, 2006-12-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_72)
- Brian Walt of Rabbis for Human Rights; Lisa Jervis and Andi Zeisler on the 10th Anniversary of Bitch Magazine; Joann Sfar on The Rabbi's Cat, 2006-12-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_98)
- Rashid Khalidi [2015-018], circa 2007-2011 (Box 20, Item 718_1013)
- Rabbi Marc Gellman [2015-021], circa 2007-2014 (Box 20, Item 718_1018)
- Geoffrey Aronson on Israeli Settlement Expansion; Sara Roy and Daniel Sievadsky on AJC Report on Anti-Semitic Jews, 2007-01-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_124)
- Rev. Osagyefo Sekou on 1/27 March and Martin Luther King, Jr.; Jim Hoberman and Richard Pena on Jewish Film Festival; Michael Ratner Remembers Bob Boehm; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Remembers Tillie Olsen, 2007-01-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_131)
- Rashid Khalidi for 2/4/2007 Marathon, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_112)
- Ali Abunimah on One Country: Introduction and Reading (Track 1), Interview (Track 2), 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_115)
- Ruchama Marton, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_123)
- Marathon: Ali Abunimah on One Country: A Bold Proposal to End the Israeli-Palestinian Impasse; Rashid Khalidi on The Iron Cage: The Story of the Palestinian Struggle for Statehood; Dr. Ruchama Marton on the Israeli Committee for the Right of Residency; Dr. Tarik Ramahi on Efforts to Enter Israel, Disc 2, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_166)
- Marathon Special, 2007-02-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_169)
- Interview with Shulamit Aloni on Jimmy Carter's Book Palestine: Peace Not Apartheid, 2007-02-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0805)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on the New Congress; Ed Case on Jewish Population Surveys; Rebecca Manski on Negev Development Plans, 2007-02-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_167)
- Shulamit Aloni and Steven Friedman on Apartheid and Israel, 2007-02-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_116)
- Neil Baldwin on Mitt Romney's Presidential Candidacy Announcement; Shulamit Aloni and Steven Freedman on Apartheid and Israel; James Shapiro on Theater for a New Audience Productions of The Merchant of Venice and The Jew of Malta, 2007-02-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_168)
- Phyllis Bennis on Iran: How Likely is War?; Steven Beeber on The Heebie-Jeebies at CBGBs: a Secret History of Jewish Punk, 2007-02-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_163)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, 2007-03-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_121)
- Udi Aloni on Effort by Israeli Consulate in Paris to Prevent His Film Forgiveness from Opening at the Israeli Film Festival; Sarita Gupta and Sheldon Freedman on the Employee Free Choice Act; Michael Weinstein on With God on Our Side: One Man's War Against an Evangelical Coup in America's Military, 2007-03-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_155)
- Peter Miller on Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-03-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0808)
- Sue Udry on Anti-war Proposals in Congress and 3/18 Demonstration in New York City; Julie Wiener on Her In the Mix Column; Iver Bernstein on New York Divided: Slavery and the Civil War Exhibition, 2007-03-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_170)
- Eric Sawyer on Act-Up's 20th Anniversary; Alexander Nowak and Atina Grossman on Germany's Re-naturalization Program; Andre Schiffrin on A Political Education: Coming of Age in Paris and New York, 2007-03-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_165)
- J.J. Goldberg, 2007-03-21 (Box 19, Item 718_0813)
- Tanya Reinhardt Remembrance; J.J. Goldberg on American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) Conference and Vice President Cheney; Nan Rubin Interviews Michael Dorf; Abe Valez Interviews Frank London, 2007-03-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0799)
- J.J. Goldberg on Cheney's AIPAC Speech, 2007-03-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_113)
- Remembering Tanya Reinhardt; J.J. Goldberg on Dick Cheney's Speech at the Annual AIPAC Assembly; Michael Dorfman on the Downtown Jewish Cultural Scene; Frank London on the Klezmatics' Emmy Award for their Woody Guthrie CD, 2007-03-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_184)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti, 2007-04-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_120)
- Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism, 2007-04-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_164)
- Phyllis Bennis on Riyadh Summit; Rachel Kahn-Troster on Admission of LGBTQ to the Jewish Theological Seminary; Alicia Svigals on Her Series at The Stone, 2007-04-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_162)
- Chris Hedges on American Fascists: The Christian Right and the War on America; Annette Ezekiel, Leader of the Band Golem, 2007-04-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_161)
- Scott Sherman and Rashid Khalidi on The New York Sun at Five Years; Natasha Winegar and Anderson Fils-Aime on New York is Our Home Campaign; Laurel Reuter on Los Desaparecidos Exhibition, 2007-04-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_159)
- Sarah Henry and Moe Fishman on Fighting Fascism: New York and the Spanish Civil War; Yousef Jabareen on The Future Vision of the Palestinian Arabs in Israel; Yael Lehrer Interview, 2007-04-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_158)
- Peter Miller on The Internationale, Part 1, 2007-04-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0818)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-04-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0822)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06 (Box 19, Item 718_0817)
- Gail Levin on Becoming Judy Chicago; Seymour Lachman on Three Men in a Room; Rachel Leon on Reforming New York State's Dysfunctional Government System, 2007-05-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_157)
- The Internationale with Peter Miller, Part 2, 2007-05-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_152)
- Marathon Special on The Internationale with Peter Miller (Partial), Part 1, 2007-05-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_156)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz interviews Rebecca Goldstein on Betraying Spinoza; Lore Segal on Shakespeare's Kitchen, 2007-05-22 (Box 19, Item 718_0812)
- Paul Buhle and Jenny Romaine on the 110th Anniversary of the Forward with Bintel Brief Readings; Abe Velez and Esther Kaplan Interview Ido Haar about 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27 (Box 19, Item 718_0820)
- Ido Haar on 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_111)
- Abe Velez and Esther Kaplan Interview Ido Haar about His Film 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_122)
- Paul Buhle and Jenny Romaine on the 110th Anniversary of the Forward; Ido Haar on His Film 9 Star Hotel, 2007-05-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_153)
- Josh Ruebner on "The World Says No to Israeli Occupation" Rally, 2007-06-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_117)
- Joyce Antler with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-06-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_126)
- Josh Ruebner on the US Campaign to End the Israel Occupation Rally 6/10-6/11; Alana Newhouse on A Living Lens: Photographs of Jewish Life from the Pages of the Forward; Joyce Antler on You Never Call! You Never Write!, 2007-06-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_160)
- Tom Segev on 1967: Israel, the War, and the Year That Transformed the Middle East at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun (Partial), 2007-06-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_176)
- Abba Eban Addresses U.N. June 1967; Mouin Rabbani on Six Day War and Fallout; Tom Segev Talk at B'nai Jeshurun, 2007-06-10 (Box 19, Item 718_0801)
- 40th Anniversary of 1967 War: Abba Eban UN Address in June 1967, Mouin Rabbani Speaks from Jordan about 1967 and Its Consequences, Tom Segev from His Talk at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun, 2007-06-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_154)
- Aziz Abu Sarah of Parents Circle; Martin Duberman on His Book Cures; Arthur Goldberg of Jews Offering New Alternatives for Healing (JONAH), 2007-07-01 (Box 19, Item 718_0804)
- Aziz Abu Sarah on Palestinian Group of Parents Circle Families Forum (October 2006 Interview), 2007-07-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_100)
- Interview with Arthur Goldberg of JONAH, 2007-07-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_118)
- Aziz Abu Sarah of Palestinian Parents Circle-Families Forum; Martin Doberman on His Attempts at Reparative Therapy and His Book Cures; Arthur Goldberg of JONAH, 2007-07-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_148)
- Arthur Goldberg on JONAH and Jewish Reparative Therapy, 2007-07-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_179)
- Michel Warschawski on Jews and the Global War and the Division of Gaza and the West Bank; Roberto Rodriguez on Baila Gitano Baila and Danzon de Moises, 2007-07-08 (Box 19, Item 718_0806)
- Michel Warschawski on Jews, the Global War, the Division of Gaza and the West Bank; Roberto Rodriguez on Baila! Gitano Baila! and El Danzon de Moises, 2007-07-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_149)
- J.J. Goldberg, 2007-07-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0823)
- J.J. Goldberg World Jewish Congress Leadership Controversy; Michael Ratner on Court Decisions on Guantanamo and Habeas Corpus; Abe Velez on Viva la Guantanamera, 2007-07-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_150)
- J.J. Goldberg on World Jewish Congress and Jewish People's Planning Institute's Future of the Jewish People in Jerusalem Conference in July 2007, 2007-07-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_171)
- J.J. Goldberg on the Future of the Jewish People in Jerusalem Conference; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Bettina F. Aptheker on Memoir Intimate Politics; Mark Laiosa Interviews Kenneth Helphand on Defiant Gardens, 2007-08-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_151)
- Bettina Aptheker on Her Memoir Intimate Politics: How I Grew up Red, Fought for Free Speech, and Became a Feminist Rebel, 2007-08-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_174)
- Mabou Mines and Miller's Launch, 2007-08-06 (Box 19, Item 718_0824)
- Rebroadcast of 11/27/2005 Show: Karen Armstrong and Chip Berlet Speaking at Examining the Real Agenda of the Religious Far Right Conference, 2007-08-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_144)
- Peter Miller on Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism Biographies, 2007-08-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_109)
- Rebroadcast of 4/10/2007 Show: Peter Miller on His Documentary Sacco and Vanzetti; Gerald Horne on The Final Victim of the Blacklist and The Color of Fascism, 2007-08-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_145)
- Stephen Walt and John Mearsheimer Book on the Israel Lobby; Rebroadcast of Phyllis Bennis with Joel Beinin (03/26/2007); Rebroadcast of Michael Massing Interview (06/11/2007), 2007-08-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_146)
- Israel Lobby with Phyllis Bennis, Joel Beinin, and Michael Massing (Rebroadcasts), 2007-08-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_181)
- Grace Paley and Moe Fishman Obituaries; Mike Wishnie on Immigrant ID Cards and ICE Raids in New Haven; Bhairavi Desai on Impending September 5 Strike Over GPS, 2007-09-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_147)
- Grace Paley Tribute with Vera Williams and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz; Eytan Fox on The Bubble, 2007-09-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0809)
- Grace Paley on Activism, Responsibility of a Poet, and on Writing with Vera Williams and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, 2007-09-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_125)
- Remembering Grace Paley with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Vera Williams; Eytan Fox on The Bubble Film, 2007-09-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_140)
- Eytan Fox on The Bubble, 2007-09-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_175)
- Debbie Howard and Mona El-Dahry on Khalil Gibran International Academy; Jennifer Siegel on Anti-Defamation League and Armenian Genocide, 2007-09-16 (Box 19, Item 718_0825)
- Deborah Howard and Mona Eldahry on Khalil Gibran International Academy; Jennifer Siegel on American Defamation League and Armenian Genocide, 2007-09-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_141)
- Roya Hakakian on US Jews and Iran; Rabbi Michael Lerner on AIPAC and Responses to Cong. Jim Moran Tikkun Interview; Dr. Zia Mian on Nuclear Policy, 2007-09-23 (Box 19, Item 718_0803)
- Roya Hakakian on U.S. Jews and Iran Policy; Michael Lerner on Rep. Jim Moran's Comments on AIPAC; Dr. Zia Mian on Nuclear Proliferation in Iran, Israel, India, and Pakistan, 2007-09-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_142)
- Jennifer Wallace, CD 1, 2007-09-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_119)
- Interviews with Dr. Jennifer Wallace, Alyson Cole, and Lore Segel, 2007-09-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_143)
- Lore Siegal on Shakespeare's Kitchen: Stories, 2007-09-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_172)
- Alyson Cole on Cult of True Victimhood: From the War on Welfare to the War on Terror, 2007-09-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_182)
- Peter Rachleff on University of St. Thomas and Desmond Tutu; Juliano Mer Khamis of the Jenin Freedom Theatre; Idan Raichel on New CD The Idan Raichel Project, 2007-10-07 (Box 19, Item 718_0802)
- Peter Rachleff on Uninviting Desmond Tutu to University of St. Thomas; Juliano Mer-Khamis of the Jenin Freedom Theater; Idan Raichel on the Idan Raichel Project, 2007-10-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_136)
- Naomi Klein on The Shock Doctrine; Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater, 2007-10-14 (Box 19, Item 718_0810)
- Marathon Special with Naomi Klein, Two Tracks, Disc 1, 2007-10-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_114)
- Marathon Special: Naomi Klein on The Shock Doctrine, Part 1, 2007-10-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_137)
- Marathon Special: Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater, Part 2, 2007-10-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_138)
- Jeremy Scahill on Blackwater: The Rise of the World's Most Powerful Mercenary Army, 2007-10-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_183)
- Barbara Olshansky on Michael Mukasey; Roger van Zwanenberg on Joel Kovel Controversy; Phyllis Bennis on Dismissal of "Los Angeles Eight" Case, 2007-11-04 (Box 19, Item 718_0815)
- Barbara Olshansky on Michael Mukasey Attorney General Nomination; Roger van Zwanenberg on Controversy Surrounding Distribution by University of Michigan Press of Joe Kovel's Overcoming Zionism; Phyllis Bennis on Dismissal of LA 8 Case After 20 Years, 2007-11-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_139)
- Akiva Eldar, 2007-11-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0800)
- Akiva Eldar on Lords of the Land, 2007-11-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_110)
- Larry Cohler-Esses and Laila al-Qabbani on Islamofascism Awareness Week; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on The Colors of Jews, 2007-11-11 (Box 19, Item 718_0821)
- Larry Cohler-Esses and Laila al-Qahtani on "Islamofascism Awareness Week" and the New McCarthyism; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on The Colors of Jews, 2007-11-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_132)
- Nan Rubin with Murray Zimiles on Gilded Lions and Jeweled Horses Exhibition, 2007-11-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_108)
- Charlie Cray on "Carried Interest" Tax; Saidiya Hartman on Lose Your Mother; Murray Zimbalist on Jewish Wood Carver Exhibit, 2007-11-18 (Box 19, Item 718_0798)
- Charlie Cray on Carried Interest Tax Reform; Saidiya Hartman on Lose Your Mother; Murray Zimiles on Gilded Lions & Jeweled Horses Exhibition, 2007-11-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_133)
- Saidiya Hartman on Lost Your Mother: A Journey Along the Atlantic Slave Route, 2007-11-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_177)
- Saidiya Hartman, 2007-11-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_178)
- Akiva Eldar and Naomi Klein, 2007-11-25 (Box 19, Item 718_0811)
- Akiva Eldar on Israeli Settler Movement; Naomi Klein on Shock Doctrine, 2007-11-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_134)
- Mikado (Michel Warschawski), 2007-11-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0819)
- Michel Warschawski on Annapolis Talks; Danny Fingeroth on Jews and Comics; D.J. Handler and Smadar Levi on the Sephardic Jewish Music Festival, 2007-12-02 (Box 19, Item 718_0816)
- Michel Warschawski on Annapolis Talks; Nan Rubin with Danny Fingeroth on Jews and Comics; D.J. Handler and Smadar Levi on the Sephardic Jewish Music Festival, 2007-12-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_135)
- Michel Warschawski on the Annapolis Conference, 2007-12-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_173)
- Michael German on the Violent Radicalization and Homegrown Terrorism Prevention Act; Diane Crispo and Stefan Shaefer on Arranged; Alisa Solomon on Hanukkah, 2007-12-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0814)
- Michael German on the Violent Radicalization and Homegrown Terrorism Prevention Act; Stefan Schaefer and Diane Crespo on Arranged; Co-host Alisa Solomon on Hanukkah, 2007-12-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_128)
- Avner Cohen on Israel and the Bomb; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Ruth Behar on An Island Called Home, 2007-12-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_129)
- Avner Cohen on Nuclear Policy between US and Israel by Nixon and Meier, 2007-12-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_180)
- Remembering: Bob Boehm, Tillie Olsen, Tanya Reinhart, Moe Fishman, and Grace Paley, 2007-12-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0807)
- Obituaries: Bob Boehm, Tillie Olsen, Tanya Reinhart, Moe Fishman, and Grace Paley, 2007-12-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_127)
- Remembering Bob Boehm, Tillie Olsen, Tanya Reinhart, Moe Fishman, and Grace Paley, 2007-12-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_130)
- Josh Ruebner [2015-017], circa 2008-2013 (Box 20, Item 718_1015)
- Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj, 2008-01-02 (Box 19, Item 718_0827)
- Hoberman Tribute at the Museum of the Moving Image, Introduction by David Schwartz, 2008-01-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_206)
- Steve Goose and Josh Ruebner on Cluster Bombs; Anthony Weiss on Yechiel Eckstein and Jewish Agency; Jim Hoberman Tribute, 2008-01-06 (Box 19, Item 718_0850)
- Steve Goose and Josh Ruebner on Efforts to Ban Cluster Bombs; Anthony Weiss on Yechiel Eckstein and the Jewish Agency; Jim Hoberman Tribute at the Museum of the Moving Image, 2008-01-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_210)
- Primo Levi Readings by Hanon Reznikov, Robert Gordon, and Ann Goldstein (Partial), 2008-01-13 (Box 19, Item 718_0826)
- Primo Levi Special with Robert Gordon and Anna Goldstein, Readings by Hanon Reznikov, 2008-01-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_208)
- Excerpts from BBC Broadcast After Death of Primo Levi: Turin, Fascism/Chemistry, Partisan, 2008-01-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_254)
- Dalit Baum, WhoProfits.org; David Heilbronner on Waiting for Armageddon; Juan Mandelbaum on Nuestros Desaparecidos, 2008-01-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_249)
- Jennifer Siegal on Obama Smear Emails; Combatants for Peace, Bassam Aramin and Yonatan Shapira, Call for Non-Violent Solutions to Israeli Occupation; Excerpt from Martin Luther King, Jr.'s April 1967 Speech, "Why I Am Opposed to the War in Vietnam", 2008-01-20 (Box 19, Item 718_0849)
- Jennifer Siegal on Resurrection of Obama Smear Emails; Bassam Aramin and Yonatan Shapiro on Combatants for Peace US Tour and Abir's Community Garden Project; Excerpt from Martin Luther King, Jr.'s Speech "Why I Am Opposed to the War in Vietnam", 2008-01-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_250)
- Jennifer Siegal on the Jewish Vote; Rebecca Goldstein on Betraying Spinoza; Scott Elliot on Mike Leigh's Play 2000 years, 2008-01-27 (Box 20, Item 718_0861)
- Roberta Brandes Gratz "Restoration Lessons" Talk at Eldridge Street Synagogue, 2008-01-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_203)
- Jennifer Siegel about Jewish Role in Primaries and Campaign to Tarnish Obama; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Rebecca Goldstein on Betraying Spinoza; Alisa Solomon Interviews Scott Elliott on Mike Leigh's Two Thousand Years, 2008-01-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_248)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz interviews Rebecca Goldstein on Betraying Spinoza, 2008-01-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_257)
- Eyad El-Sarraj, 2008-02-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_189)
- Interview with Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj, Human Rights Activist in Gaza, 2008-02-03; cuid34402 (Box 17, Audiocassette 718_0656)
  Duration: 0:08:51, Preservation Note: Program Recorded at a Very High Level at Times; Phasing During Program; Program Distorted at Times
- Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj and Dr. Sara Roy on Gaza; Nan Rubin with Roberta Brandes Gratz on Renovation of Eldridge Street Synagogue, 2008-02-03 (Box 19, Item 718_0856)
- Sara Roy, 2008-02-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_190)
- Gaza with Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj and Dr. Sara Roy; Roberta Brandes Gratz at the Rededication of Eldridge Street Synagogue, 2008-02-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_247)
- Dr. Eyad El-Sarraj, Dr. Sara Roy, 2008-02-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_258)
- Eyad El-Sarraj, 2008-02-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_262)
- Readings: Tess Slesinger, "Jobs in the Sky"; Mike Gold, "The Soul of the Landlord"; Jenny Romaine, "The Day Santa Claus Fainted", 2008-02-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_207)
- Great Depression Readings and Music, 2008-02-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_243)
- Jeffrey Shandler, 2008-02-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_201)
- Ari Berman on Farrakhan in the Democratic Debate, 2008-03-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_211)
- Jeffrey Shandler Discussion on The Counterfeiters", 2008-03-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_253)
- Marion Kaplan on Dominican Haven; Mitchell Plitnick on Israel Negotiations with Hamas Over Gaza; Julia Meltzer, David Thorne, and Rami Farah on Their Pieces in the Whitney Biennial, 2008-03-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0848)
- Marion Kaplan and Abe Velez on Sosúa Exhibition at Museum of Jewish Heritage; Mitchell Plitnick on Gaza; David Thorne, Julia Meltzer and Rami Farah on Syria Video at Whitney Biennial, 2008-03-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_212)
- Leslie Cagan; Joel Beinin on Israel/Palestine Conflict for Egypt; Eric Schneiderman on Politics (Partial), 2008-03-16 (Box 19, Item 718_0855)